{
    "id": "51dbdf5fc6b94ce295f9f8870089e928",
    "title": "Yourself / yourselves | Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c21507e999404b9f80a453a436682ae0",
            "title": "Reflexive Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "His letters are all about ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "himself",
                        "him",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Peter, if you work like this, you will make ……………….. ill.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yourself",
                        "yourselves"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They talk to …………………. a lot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "themself",
                        "themselves"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long have you guys known ………………….?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yourself",
                        "yourselves",
                        "each other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "These shoes are designed for sprinters like …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you",
                        "yourself",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you ………………….. on Sundays?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shave",
                        "shave yourself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She took her dog with ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "her",
                        "herself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are very selfish. You only think of ……………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you",
                        "yourself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am quite pleased with ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "me",
                        "myself"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everybody came early except ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "me",
                        "myself",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}